Register of the United States National Student Association International Commission records
Hoover Institution Archives
- NATIONAL UNIONS OF STUDENTS FILE, 1947-1966
  - Geographical file
    - Hungary, International reactions to Hungarian Revolution, 1957
    - Hungary, International Rescue Committee, 1957-1958
    - Hungary, language training, 1956-1957
    - Hungary, news reports, 1956-1957
    - Hungary, scholarship possibilities, 1957-1958
    - Hungary, schools and organizations reactions to Hungarian uprising, 1956-1957 (Box 216)
    - Hungary, Union of Free Hungarian Students, 1957-1958
    - Hungary, United Federation of Hungarian Students, 1964-1965
    - Hungary, World University Service, 1956-1957
    - Iceland, 1955-1965 (Box 217)
    - India, 1947-1957
    - India, 1957-1963 (Box 218)
    - India, 1963-1964 (Box 219)
    - Indochina, 1949-1950, 1953, 1959-1960
    - Indonesia, 1955-1958
    - Indonesia, 8-63, 1945 (Box 220)
    - Iran, 1949-1963
    - Iraq, 1957-1966 (Box 221)
    - Ireland, 1946-1966
    - Iron Curtain countries, 1957-1958
    - Israel, 1947-1956
    - Israel, 1957-1966 (Box 222)
    - Italy, 1947-1951
    - Italy, 1951-1960 (Box 223)
    - Italy, 1960-1965 (Box 224)
    - Ivory Coast, 1959-1967
    - Jamaica, 1954-1964
    - Japan, 1947-1952
    - Japan, 1953-1956 (Box 225)
    - Japan, 1956-1962 (Box 226)
    - Japan, 1962-1964 (Box 227)
    - Jordan, 1953-1964
    - Kenya, 1962-1967
    - Korea, 1949-1967
    - Kuwait, 1965-1966
    - Kuwait, 1965-1966 (Box 318)
    - Laos, 1958-1963 (Box 227)
    - Latin America, Archives of the NSA, 1946-1962
    - Latin America, Sub-Commission correspondence, 1958
    - Latin America, general, 1948-1952
    - Latin America, general, 1952-1960 (Box 228)
    - Latin America, general, 1960-1965 (Box 229)
    - Latin America, NSA policies, 1946-1952 (Box 230)
    - Latin America student conference, 1956-1963
    - Latin America student seminars, 1962-1963
    - Lebanon, 1947-1966
    - Liberia, 1947-1967 (Box 231)
    - Libya, 1955-1964
    - Luxembourg, 1952-1965
    - Madagascar, 1956-1965
    - Malawi, 1964-1966
    - Malaya, 1947-1964
    - Malaysia, 1964-1966
    - Mali, 1962-1963
    - Malta, 1963-1965
    - Mauritania, 1961 (Box 232)
    - Mexico, 1947-1966
    - Mexico, miscellaneous (Box 233)
    - Middle East, general, 1947-1967
    - Morocco, 1955-1966 (Box 234)
    - Mozambique, 1960-1966 (Box 235)
    - Nepal, 1954-1966
    - Netherlands, 1949-1965
    - New Guinea, 1960
    - New Zealand, 1947-1966 (Box 236)
    - Nicaragua, 1952-1966
    - Nigeria, 1953-1963
    - Nigeria, 1963-1966 (Box 237)
    - North Africa, 1947-1957
    - North America, 1959-1960
    - North Korea, 1962
    - North Viet Nam, 1962-1963
    - Norway, 1947-1955
    - Norway, 1956-1965 (Box 238)
    - Nyasaland, 1959-1960
    - Okinawa, 1956
    - Oman, Omani Students Association report, 1962-1963
    - Pakistan, 1951-1957
    - Pakistan, 1958-1965 (Box 239)
    - Palestine, 1948, 1961-1965
    - Palestine, 1948, 1961-1965 (Box 318)
    - Panama, 1947-1959 (Box 239)
    - Panama, 1959-1966 (Box 240)
    - Pan-America, 1953
    - Paraguay, 1951-1958
    - Paraguay, 1958-1964 (Box 241)
    - Peru, 1947-1966
    - Philippines, 1947 (Box 242)
    - Poland, 1947-1958
    - Poland, 1958-1965 (Box 243)
    - Portugal, 1956-1967
    - Portuguese Africa, 1964-1966 (Box 244)
    - Portuguese Guinea, 1963-1966
    - Puerto Rico, 1948-1962
    - Puerto Rico, 1962-1965 (Box 245)
    - Red China, 1965-1966
    - Rhodesia, 1958-1967
    - Ruanda-Urundi, 1959-1961, 1965 (Box 246)
    - Rumania, 1948-1964
    - Saar, 1953-1957
    - Scandinavia, 1947-1955
    - Scotland, 1947-1965
    - Senegal, 1943-1967 (Box 247)
    - Sierra Leone, 1953-1966
    - Singapore, 1959-1966
    - Somalia, 1959-1964
    - Southern Rhodesia, 1962-1965
    - Southeast Asia, 1964
    - Southwest Africa, undated
    - South Africa, 1948-1957 (Box 248)
    - South Africa, 1957-1958 (Box 249)
    - South Africa, 1958-1961 (Box 250)
    - South Africa, 1962-1964 (Box 251)
    - South Africa, 1964-1967 (Box 252)
    - South Africa, Robert F. Kennedy trip to South Africa, 1965
    - South Korea, 1960-1966 (Box 253)
    - South Viet Nam, 1960-1964
    - Spain, 1947-1956
    - Spain, 1956-1966 (Box 254)
    - Sudan, 1953-1963 (Box 255)
    - Surinam, 1964
    - Swaziland, 1963-1965
    - Sweden, 1948-1951
    - Switzerland, 1948-1959
    - Switzerland, 1959-1965 (Box 256)
    - Syria, 1947-1965
    - Taiwan, undated
    - Tanganyika, 1958-1964
    - Tanzania, 1965-1966
    - Thailand, 1948-1963
    - Togo, 1961, 1963, 1967 (Box 257)
    - Tunisia, 1952-1966
    - Turkey, 1947-1965
    - Uganda, 1954-1966 (Box 258)
    - Ukraine, 1950-1965
    - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1947-1958
    - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1958-1962 (Box 259)
    - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1963-1966 (Box 260)
    - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, Moscow Youth Forum, 1964 September
    - United Arab Republic, 1961-1966
    - United States, 1965
    - Upper Volta, 1962-1963
    - Uruguay, 1949-1956
    - Uruguay, 1956-1966 (Box 261)
    - Venezuela, 1952-1959
    - Venezuela, 1959-1967 (Box 262)
    - Vietnam, 1948-1966
    - Wales, 1952-1953
    - West Africa, 1951-1966 (Box 263)
    - West Germany, 1963-1965
    - West India, West Indian Students' Union, 1947-1954
    - West Irian (Indonesia Territory), 1960, 1962
    - West Indies, 1956-1966
    - World wide (general), 1948-1956
    - Yugoslavia, 1947-1954
    - Yugoslavia, 1954-1966 (Box 264)
    - Zambia, 1963-1966
    - Zanzibar, 1962
  - NUS miscellaneous publications
- SUBJECT FILE OF ORGANIZATIONS, 1946-1966
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, bulletins, newsclippings, and brochures relating to various organizations of interest to the International Commission, arranged alphabetically by name of organization.
  - Afghanistan Student Association of the U.S.A., 1954-1964 (Box 265)
  - African-American Affairs Association, 1966-1967
  - African-American Chamber of Commerce, 1964-1966
  - African-American Institute, Inc., 1957-1967
  - African-American Student Foundation, 1960-1962
  - African Freedom Fund, 1963
  - African Refugee Scholarship Program, 1962
  - African Scholarship Committee, Inc., 1964-1965
  - African Service Institute, 1966
  - African Student Organizations in Europe, 1963
  - African Student Service, 1963
  - All-China Student Federation, 1949-1962
  - All-African Students Union of the Americas, 1953
  - Alliance for Progress, 1965
  - Amateur Athletic Union, 1964-1965
  - American Academy of Asian Students, 1954
  - American-Asian Education Exchange, Inc., 1960
  - American Association for the United Nations, 1954-1963 (Box 266)
  - American Association of International Relations Clubs, undated
  - American Association of University Professors, 1953
  - American Association of University Women, 1957
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1956-1959
  - American Committee for Cultural Freedom, 1953
  - American Committee on Africa, 1956-1967
  - American Committee on United Europe, 1952, 1957-1963
  - American Council of Voluntary Agencies for Foreign Service, Inc., 1952
  - American College on College Study in Switzerland, 1948 (Box 267)
  - American Council on Education, 1949-1955
  - American Council on Education, 1955-1957
  - American Council on Education, 1957-1962
  - American Council on Education, Commission on Education and International Affairs, 1955- (Box 268)
  - American Council on Judaism, 1962-1963
  - American Council on NATO, Inc., 1953-1954
  - American Express Company, 1953-1954
  - American Federation of International Institutes, 1956
  - American Field Service, 1966
  - American Friends of the Middle East, Inc., undated
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1947-1961
  - American Heritage Foundation, 1953
  - American Immigration Conference, 1955-1958
  - American Institute of Pacific Relations, 1957 (Box 269)
  - American Latvian Youth Association, 1948-1958
  - American Society of African Culture, 1960-1966
  - American University of Beirut, 1956
  - American Youth for Democracy, 1947-1950
  - American Youth for a Free World, 1947-1949
  - American Youth Hostels, 1955-1961
  - American Youth Projects Abroad, 1955
  - American Zionist Council, 1956
  - Americans for Democratic Action, 1947-1961
  - Amnesty International U.S.A., 1967
  - Arab Students Union in the United Kingdom and Ireland, 1964
  - Asia Foundation, 1955-1963
  - Asia Institute, 1957-1958
  - Asia Society, 1957-1960 (Box 270)
  - Asian Student Press Bureau, 1963
  - Asian and African Students and Youth, 1957
  - Associated Collegiate Press, 1951-1953
  - Association for International Student work, 1953
  - Association of Hungarian Students in the United States, 1960-1966
  - Associations of Institutions and Agencies in the New York Area Assisting Foreign Students, 1948
  - Association International of Students in Sciences, Economics and Commerce, 1954-1960
  - Association of International Relations Clubs, 1955-1961
  - Association of Internes and Medical Students, 1947-1950
  - Association of Polish Students in Exile, 1962
  - Atlantic Union Committee, Inc., 1956
  - B'nai B'rith, 1950-1954
  - CARE, 1947-1950
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1948-1961
  - Carnegie Endowment International Center, 1954-1955
  - Catholic Interracial Council, 1960
  - Central African Students Association, 1964
  - Central American Student Congress, 1961
  - China Institute in America, 1947-1952
  - Chicago Council of American Soviet Friendship, 1956
  - Church World Service, Inc., 1947
  - Citizens Food Committee, 1947
  - Citizenship Clearing House, 1947-1948 (Box 271)
  - College English Association, 1950
  - College News Conferences, 1957-1961
  - College Press Conferences, 1955-1956
  - Collegiate Council for the United Nations, 1947-1961
  - Colonial Student Organizations, 1956-1957
  - Columbia College Citizenship Council, 1966
  - Commission for International Education Reconstruction, 1948-1949
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1952-1953
  - Committee for Free Asia, Inc., 1951-1955
  - Committee for International Student Cooperation, 1948
  - Committee for World Development and World Disarament, 1953
  - Committee on Educational Interchange Policy, 1955
  - Committee on Friendly Relations Among Foreign Students, 1947
  - Committee on International Exchange of Persons, 1954
  - Community Development Project, Inc., 1950-1951
  - Committee for World Youth Friendship and Cultural Exchange, 1951
  - Confluence Magazine, 1953
  - Congolese Students Union of the Americas, 1962
  - Congregational Christian Service Committee, 1952, 1955
  - Congress for Cultural Freedom, 1952, 1955
  - Congress of European American Associations (Belgium), 1956
  - Cosmopolitan Clubs, 1947
  - Council for International visitors, 1960-1961
  - Council of African Organizations, 1965
  - Council on International Educational Projects, 1948-1949 (Box 272)
  - Council on Race and Caste in World Affairs, 1958-1959
  - Council on Student Travel, 1951-1958
  - Council on Student Travel, 1958-1961
  - Council on Student Travel, 1961-1963
  - Consultative Assembly of the European Council, 1956 (Box 273)
  - Consultative Council on South Africa, 1965-1967
  - Crossroads Student Center, 1953
  - Democratic National Committee, 1957
  - East African Students Union in the Americas, 1962-1964
  - Eastern World, L961
  - Economic Club of Detroit, 1947-1949
  - European Student Mirror, 1952
  - European Student Theatre Union, 1955-1956
  - Experiment in International Living, 1947-1960, 1963
  - Federation of Students from Black Africa in France (FEANF), 1955-1959
  - Federation of Indian Student Associations (FISA), 1965
  - Federation of International Associations of Engineering Students, 1954-1958 (Box 274)
  - Federation of All African Students, 1963
  - Federation of International Sport Universitaire, 1951-1961
  - Federation of International Sport Universitaire, 1962-1966 (Box 275)
  - Federation of North African Students in France, 1955
  - Federation of Ukrainian Catholic Student Unions (exile), 1956
  - Federation of Ukrainian Student Organizations of America, 1955-1963
  - Federation of Universities of Argentina, 1962-1963
  - Ford Foundation, 1963
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1953-1959 (Box 276)
  - Foreign Student Organizations in U.S., 1955-1963
  - Formosan Student Organizations in U.S., 1962
  - Foundation for Youth and Student Affairs, 1962-1965
  - Foundation Library Service, 1957
  - Foundations (general), 1966-1967
  - Free Europe College (France), 1952
  - Free Europe Committee, Inc., 1956-1957
  - Freedom House, 1960-1961
  - Friends Committee on National Legislation, 1953-1955
  - Friends of the Association (USNSA), 1952-1953
  - Friendly Relations with Overseas Students, 1953
  - Friend for the Republic, 1955-1956
  - General Union of Palestine Students, 1965-1966
  - Ghana Student Union in U.S., 1963
  - Greater New York Council for Foreign Students, 1949-1954
  - Good Neighbor Foundation, 1947
  - Harvard University, 1954-1957
  - Independence Foundation, 1962-1963
  - India League of American, 1951-1952
  - Indo-American Club, 1953
  - Indonesian Student Association in U.S., 1956-1964
  - Institute of European Studies, 1957-1959
  - Institute for Foreign Junior Technicians, 1953
  - Institute for International Youth Affairs, Inc., 1962, 1966 (Box 277)
  - Institute of International Education, 1947-1950
  - Institute of International Education, 1951-1956
  - Institute of International Education, 1956-1958
  - Institute of International Education, 1958-1959 (Box 278)
  - Institute of International Education, 1959-1960
  - Institute of International Education, 1960-1962
  - Institute of International Relations, Stanford, 1949 (Box 279)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations, 1953
  - Institute of World Affairs, Inc., 1947-1958
  - Inter-American Association for Democracy and Freedom, 1955, 1960
  - Inter-American Student Confederation, 1957
  - Intercollegiate Chess League of America, 1957-1958
  - Interdenominational Commission on Youth Service Project, undated
  - International Assembly of Muslim Youth, undated
  - International Association for Exchange of Students for Technical Experience, 1951-1965
  - International Association of Dental Students, 1955-1960
  - International Association of University Professors and Lecturers, 1956
  - International Association of Universities, 1951, 1956, 1959
  - International Commission of Jurists, 1959
  - International Communist Front Organizations, 1965
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1953-1955
  - International Congress of Slavists, 1955
  - International Council of Exiled Student Organizations, 1951
  - International Development Placement Association, 1952-1954
  - International Educational Programs, 1950
  - International Farm Youth Exchange, 1953
  - International Federation of Medical Student Associations, 1951-1960 (Box 280)
  - International Federation of Musical Youth, 1956
  - International Forum for Peace, 1952-1953
  - International House Association, 1946-1960
  - International Labour Office, 1955
  - International League for the Rights of Man, 1951
  - International League of Students, 1954-1955
  - International Medical Cooperation Committee, 1950-1951
  - International Pharmaceutical Students Federation, 1956
  - International Rescue Committee, 1955-1957
  - International School of America, 1960-1961
  - International Student Association of Japan, 1965-1966
  - International Student Assembly, 1942
  - International Student Association of Greater Boston, 1956-1959
  - International Student Center, 1949
  - International Student Council, 1963
  - International Student Movement for the United Nations, 1956-1961
  - International Student Service, 1947-1949
  - International Student Service, 1949-1961 (Box 281)
  - International Union of Socialist Youth, 1955-1957
  - International Union of Young Christian Democrats, 1965
  - Iranian Students Association in the U.S., 1953-1966 (Box 282)
  - Iraqi Students Society in the United Kingdom, 1955
  - Israel Students Organization in the U.S., 1954-1966
  - Ivy Network, 1955 (Box 283)
  - Japan Society, 1955
  - Joint Committee for Student Action, 1947-1949
  - Joint Committee for Student Action, 1947-1949 (Box 318)
  - Junior Press Conference, 1953 (Box 283)
  - Junior Year Abroad, 1948-1949
  - Kettering Foundation, 1967
  - Koinonia Foundation, 1954-1955
  - Korean-American Cultural Association, 1952
  - Korean-American Scholarship Committee, 1956
  - Korean Student Organization in the U.S., 1960-1961
  - Labor Youth League, 1954-1957
  - Latvian Student World Association, 1956-1965
  - League of Women Voters, 1950
  - Lisle Fellowship, Inc., 1954-1955
  - Lithuanian Student Association, Inc., 1957, 1961
  - Maryknoll International Student Committee, 1961
  - Men of Goodwill, 1947-1948
  - Midwest Committee on Discriminations in Higher Education, 1954
  - Miscellaneous, 1947-1961
  - Moral Rearmament, 1957-1958
  - Mozambican Institute, 1966-1967
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1955-1956 (Box 284)
  - National Association for Foreign Student Affairs, 1964-1967
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1958-1961
  - National Association of Foreign Student Advisers, 1947-1954
  - National Association of Foreign Student Advisers, 1954-1957
  - National Association of Foreign Student Advisers, 1958-1965
  - National Catholic Action Study Commission, 1953 (Box 285)
  - National Catholic Welfare Conferences, 1958, 1961
  - National Citizens Committee for Columbus Day, 1955
  - National Committee for an Adequate Oversees U.S. Information Program, 1955-1956
  - National Committee on Immigration and Citizenship, 1955
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, Inc., 1953
  - National Conference on Economic and Social Development, 1956
  - National Conference on Exchange of Persons, 1960
  - National Convocation on Immigration and Naturalization, 1956
  - National Council on Arts, Sciences, and Professions, 1951
  - National Council on Immigration and Citizenship, 1957
  - National Education Association, 1950-1958
  - National Federation of Canadian University Students, 1949
  - National Federation of Catholic College Students, 1947-1960
  - National Intercollegiate Christian Council, 1947-1948, 1950
  - National Inter-Fraternity Council, 1947
  - National Newman Club Federation, 1949-1960
  - National Scholarship Service and Fund for Negro Students, 1952-1956
  - National Self Government Committee, 1947
  - National Social Welfare Assembly, 1953-1961
  - National Student Christian Federation, 1965-1967
  - National Student Federation of America, 1931-1950 (Box 286)
  - National Union of Bahraini Students, 1965-1966
  - National Union of Czechoslovak Students in Exile, 1955
  - National Union of Ethiopian University Students, 1967
  - National Union of Israeli Students, 1965-1966
  - National Union of Nigerian Students, 1967
  - National Union of South African Students, 1966-1967
  - National Union of South West African Students, 1966-1967
  - National Union of Tanzanian Students, 1966
  - National Union of Zambian Students, 1967
  - Near East College Association, 1953-1957
  - New York Herald Tribune Forum, 1953
  - New York State Citizens' Council, Inc., 1952
  - New York Times, 1957
  - New Zealand University Student Press Association, 1964
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1955-1961
  - Nigerian Student Union of the Americas, 1966-1967
  - North American Congress on Latin America, 1966-1967
  - North American Student Cooperative League, 1950
  - Office of Relations, Students of Latin America, 1960 (Box 287)
  - One World Seminar for Schools, 1953
  - Organization of American States, 1959-1961
  - Organization of Arab Students in the U.S., 1956-1966
  - Organization of Iranian Students, 1961
  - Organization of Universal Universities, 1954
  - Organization of Polish Students in Exile, 1956
  - Pacificana, 1958 (Box 288)
  - Pakistan Students Association of America, 1954-1966
  - Pan African Students Organization in the Americas, Inc., 1962-1967
  - Pan American Development Foundation, Inc., 1965-1967
  - Pan American Union, 1956-1963 (Box 289)
  - Pax Romana, 1948-1965
  - Peace Corps, 1960-1966 (Box 290)
  - Pen Friend Clubs of Japan, 1954
  - People-to-People Foundation, 1957-1958
  - Plan for the Mutual Aid and the Education of Students, 1952
  - Progressive Citizens of America, 1947
  - Progressive Youth Organizing Committee, 1960
  - Permias, 1962-1963
  - Radio Free Europe, 1953-1958
  - Refugee Conference, 1959
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1963-1964 (Box 314)
  - Southeast Asia Treaty Organization, 1959-1962 (Box 290)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1952
  - South Africa Freedom Action Committee, 1965
  - South African National Student Press Association, 1966-1967
  - Southern African Public Opinion Seminar, 1966
  - Southern School News, 1958-1963
  - South West African Student Union in the U.S., 1966
  - Student American Medical Association, 1954
  - Student League for Industrial Democracy, 1953-1958 (Box 318)
  - Student Mirror, 1953-1963 (Box 290)
  - Student Peace Union, 1960
  - Student Project for Amenity Among Nations, 1947-1950
  - Student Volunteer Movement, 1955
  - Students for a Democratic Society, 1966
  - Students for America, 1952-1953
  - Students for Democratic Action, 1953-1961 (Box 318)
  - Students International Union, 1947 (Box 290)
  - Syracuse African Seminar, 1966
  - Texas Intercollegiate Student Association, 1956 (Box 292)
  - Turkish Students Association of New York, 1954-1963
  - Union of Free Hungarian Students, 1959-1961
  - Union des Grandes Ecoles (France), 1954-1959
  - Union of Latin American Universities, 1956-1957
  - Unipress, 1948-1949
  - United Council on World Affairs, 1950-1953
  - United Federation of Hungarian Students, 1961-1966
  - United Nations, 1950-1965
  - United Nations Association, 1947-1954 (Box 293)
  - United Nations Day, 1949-1956
  - United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization, 1958-1961
    - General
    - NSA policy correspondence, 1947-1951
    - NSA representative on National Commission, correspondence, 1948-1953
    - NSA Youth Leadership Training Conference, 1951 (Box 294)
  - United Nations non-governmental organizations, 1955-1960
  - U.S. Army, 1956
  - U.S. Christian Council, 1958
  - U.S. Committee for the United Nations, 1955-1961
  - U.S. Government
    - General, 1947-1961
    - Department of Justice, Immigration Service, 1952
    - Federal Security Agency, Office of Education, 1948
    - Economic Cooperation Agency, 1950-1951
    - State Department
      - Exchange of Persons, 1947-1952
      - J. W. Fulbright Board, 1948-1953 (Box 295)
      - Voice of America, undated
    - Veterans Administration, 1949-1952
  - U.S. Information Agency, 1954-1960
  - U.S. National Commission for United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organizations, 1947-1961
  - United States Olympic Committee, 1951 (Box 296)
  - United States Youth Council, 1963-1967
  - United Student Christian Council, 1949-1959
  - United World Federalists, Inc., 1947-1962
  - Universiade, 1959-1965
  - Universities Committee on the Problems of War and Peace, 1963
  - University of Chicago, 1955-1956
  - Urban League, 1963-1964
  - Vick Chemical Company, 1958 (Box 297)
  - Vietnamese Catholic Association in America, 1956, 1959
  - Vocational Advisory Service, 1956-1957
  - Voice of America, 1952-1960
  - Volharding, 1952
  - Voluntary Organizations and a World Without War, 1963-1964
  - Volunteer Teachers for Africa, 1965-1966
  - Volunteer Opportunities, Inc., 1965-1966
  - Voter Education Project, 1964
  - Voters for Peace, 1963
  - WCAU, Philadelphia, 1962
  - WMEX, Boston, 1962
  - WPEN Philadelphia, 1962
  - WVBR, Ithaca, 1962